♪ In the not too
distant future ♪
♪ Somewhere and time in space ♪
♪ Mike Nelson and
his robot pals ♪
♪ Are caught in
an endless chase ♪
♪ Pursued by a woman
whose name is Pearl ♪
♪ An evil gal who wants
to rule the world ♪
♪ She threw a few
things in her purse ♪
♪ And in her rocket
ship she hunts him ♪
♪ All across the universe ♪
♪ I'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst I can
find (la-la-la) ♪
♪ They'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And I'll monitor
his mind (la-la-la) ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies begin
or end (la-la-la) ♪
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of
his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot call call ♪
♪ Cambot (You're on) ♪
♪ Gypsy, (Oh my stars) ♪
♪ Tom Servo (Check me out) ♪
♪ Croooow (I'm different) ♪
♪ If you're wonderin' how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science
facts (la-la-la) ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ You should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(doors close loudly)
- Mike, Mike, Mike, grr!
(dog barks)
- What is going on here?
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
down, down, down, down!
What's up?
- Mike, we were playing
dog and bear, you know?
And Servo was chasing me
and I ran panicked over
logs and through streams,
maddened with primal
terror, you know?
And I turned and
raked my deadly claws
against his howling
snout, you know?
And I rose to my
hind feet, towering
and still bellowing, he came
and I mewled and spewed gore
from my wounds and snot
from my flaring wild maw,
and then we were
locked like lovers
and then I was encurled by
moiled, spotted hound bodies
and my entrails
were hangin' out.
And I tried a savage
feral roar but alas,
my force was spent and I died!
And then Servo took it
through Mars! (sobs)
- I understand, is that
what happened, Servo?
- Yeah well, I guess
that's about right.
But I mean, what's too
far when your entrails
are spilling out?
I mean, where's the line?
- Well, I see your point
but I'll tell you what,
why don't you guys just
play a nice game, okay?
- Okay.
- Could you stick my
entrails back in, Mike?
- Sure I will.
We'll be right back.
Entrails back in, there you go.
- Thank you.
- How's that?
("MST3K Love Theme")
(laughter and singing)
What's so funny, guys?
- We're having fun! (laughs)
- Oh, 'cause you're not
playing dog and bear again,
are you, 'cause you know
how that can get outta hand.
- Oh no, now we're playing
sea lion and squirrel!
And we have nothing at
all to do with each other!
- And it's fun!
- That's great!
Oh, Pearl Bailey's calling.
- Oh, hurry up!
- Hey, Nelson-eddie!
It's time to take
your movie medicine.
- Don't look!
- We're not looking!
Bobo has to
go, so Brain Boy here
tied a rope around him
and sent him out.
Anyway your movie
today is call--
- [Bobo] You're
lookin' I know you are!
- Believe me, there's nothing
I'd like to look at less!
- [Bobo] Well, I'm gonna go
into this big tunnel thing here
so you can't look at me--
- Wait, wait, don't go in there!
Don't go--
I wouldn't do that--
(Bobo shouts)
That's a
a wormhole.
- A worm what?
- A wormhole.
- A what hole?
- A wormhole!
Wormhole, a cosmic rift
where all time and matter
is rearranged seemingly
at random!
- Oh, big deal!
- Well, it is!
They're very unpredictable
and dangerous!
- Well, so am I, Brainiac,
let's get in there
and get that monkey!
- May I ask why?
- What happens if Bobo causes
one of them weird numbers
where he goes back in the
past and steps on a butterfly
or somethin' and
then 'cause of that,
mammals as we know
them never evolve
and then 'cause of that, mankind
never invents slot machines
and my favorite hobby goes
straight down the toity, huh?!
- Your logic is irrefutable.
- Hey, Nelson, we're
goin' wormhole surfing.
- Goodbye!
- So long!
Don't forget to write!
Bye!
- Goodbye!
- Bon voyage!
- À bientôt!
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
No!
You're comin' with!
Hey, Whitey, how about
usin' that brain of yours
to give these guys a tow?
- Yes, I'll do that
for you, Ma'am,
but then I gots to
be moseying along!
I got spurs that go
jingly-jangly-jingle after all,
that's just the way I am!
I'll kiss you now,
Ma'am, and then--
- [Pearl] Would you just lasso
the stupid ship, please?!
- Okay, okay!
I'll show you where all
the cowboys are goin'!
(loud crash)
- Whoa!
- We're being flaggo-busted!
- Hang on, little dowgies!
(loud whooshing)
- Whoa, whoa, that's heavy!
- We hope you enjoy traveling
Wormhole Express Airlines.
Your in-flight movie today
is a little confection
from our friends in Japan
called Prince of Space.
Sayonara!
- Wow, a wormhole, all sorts
of weird stuff could happen!
- And it probably will!
- Even worse, we
have movie sign!
(loud buzzing)
(doors opening loudly)
- [Crow] Wormhole. (chuckles)
- [Servo] Hey, I'm in
space already, damn!
- [Crow] Starring Tatsuo,
Johji, Hokiro and Ken!
Oh, Nobu, hmm!
- [Mike] So is this gonna be
a super violent porn cartoon?
- [Servo] (scoffs) The
English version done
by Bellucci Productions!
Of course, makes sense.
(sinister music)
- [Crow] HO scale, Japan!
- [Servo] Japan, by Marks!
(Servo hums)
- [Crow] Aw, Ma, tempura again?
- [Servo] We love
cram school, Father!
Okay, okay, okay, two
Italian guys dodge mushrooms
thrown by a monkey, huh?
- I don't know.
- Is that great?
As soon as you get your
rocket ship inflated,
you'll be able to fly
around in outer space!
- I'd be afraid to go out there!
Wouldn't you be afraid, Susie?
- Oh, yes! (laughs)
- Mickey!
What do you say we
watch television?
The world
championship's tonight!
- [Mike] (chuckles) Of what?
- Yes, excuse me, Mom!
(laughter)
- [Servo] Put on the
upsetting shorts!
- Wally will be coming by to
pick you up in a few minutes!
- Oh, he's never on
time, anyway, forget it!
Here, Mickey, I'll leave an
apple here for you, Kimmy.
- Thank you.
- It's just wonderful
what your friend, Wally,
has done for these children.
- Yes, he doesn't have a very
easy time of it, I imagine,
playing both mother and
father to a couple of orphans.
But he does it well.
- Yes, they're very happy
with him, as you can see.
And he's even
started teaching them
how to earn their own money!
- [Mike] More squid eyes?
- Oho, here he is now!
- Oho!
- I hope my kids haven't
been giving you much trouble.
- Of course not, we
love having them!
- Well, don't just
stand over there!
Come over here and sit down!
- Come on, Mickey, let's go in
and watch the
championship fight.
- Alright, if you want to.
- Well, son, we were all
just talking about you.
- [Wally] You were?
Something nice, I hope.
- About the way you take
care of the children.
- [Crow] You ever feed them?
- We agreed you were
doing a marvelous job.
- Oh, well, it's really nothing.
I'm trying to do my best.
I just wish I could
teach them something
besides bootblacking!
- What's the matter
with bootblacking?
We both like it very
much, right, Kimmy?
- Sure!
- So shut up
about bootblacking!
- This new rocket fuel of yours
has astounded the whole world!
- You haven't heard the latest!
The first cosmic
exploration rocket
will be launched
from this space!
- [Crow] The dining room?
- [Professor]
Come, come, my boy.
You know you were a tremendous
help to me in the laboratory.
And your friend, Dr.
Cummings of America
was also a great help.
And Susie's brother also
deserves some of the credit.
By the way, he's
coming back tomorrow.
- Oh, that's nice.
- [Mickey] Hey, what's
that supposed to be?
- That's a commercial.
- It couldn't be!
They're not selling anything.
- You wanna bet
it's a commercial?
They're probably
selling some new toy.
- [Servo] We like it very much!
- That looks like
a real rocket ship!
- [Man On TV] Attention,
people of Earth!
This is Krankor
Exploration Force speaking!
- Crank whore?
(Mike laughs)
- [Man On TV] Stand by
for an important message!
Stand by for an
important message!
- [Servo] Veterans
cannot be turned down!
- [Man On TV] The ancient
name of the dark planet.
- [Servo] Can't
believe they're showin'
Dennis Francis' butt!
- That ship must
be in outer space!
- That's a toy I wouldn't mind
having, I like it very much!
(laughter)
- Attention, people of Earth!
- Ba-cawk!
- I am Ambassador Phantom
from the planet Krankor!
- [Mike And Robots] We are Ken!
- I am rapidly
approaching your planet.
In the warship which
you have just seen.
(Mike clucks)
(robots chuckle)
- Overloading every channel!
What a powerful
beam he must have!
Look at that modulation!
- [Phantom] I will
arrive tomorrow night
at precisely eight o'clock.
(Servo clucks)
At that time, I will make
my wishes known to you!
You will obey them or die!
Have a pleasant night's
sleep! (laughs evilly)
(Crow laughs)
- How are ya?
- [Crow] Krankor,
nothing to worry about!
Truman Capote sent
to fight Krankor!
(suspenseful music)
- Hey, let's share
your little quarter!
- Hey, Wally!
- What is it, Beave?
- Hot off the press!
- Thanks!
Where are you going?
- Professor Macken's
giving a press conference.
- He's supposed to know
what these space men want.
He might know how we
can fight 'em off, too!
- Yeah, the whole bunch
of firecrackers left over
from last year!
Maybe we can use them!
(laughter)
- Let's go, we're late now!
- Goodbye!
- Goodbye, unfunny, weird men!
- [Servo] He seems
like a real jerk!
- Hey, Wally, I bet you're
afraid of those space men!
- Of course I am!
- What for?
You aren't gonna be much help
if you get frightened
as easy as that!
- [Mike] I'm not here!
- [Servo] Walter
Mondale arrives.
- [Man] Come on, fellas,
shake a leg, we're late!
- [Crow] After swingin' for
some violent porn comics!
- Oh, here he comes now!
- Good morning, Professor!
- [Servo] Mm, it's the
Subway Foundler Club!
- Good morning, gentlemen!
- Welcome to
my Grandma's living room.
- Do you have any questions?
- Yes, Professor.
What about these space men, sir?
Do we expect them to
attempt to land here?
- [Professor] Yes,
let me explain.
You know, gentlemen,
we have developed a
powerful new rocket fuel.
Now, for reasons which
must remain classified,
we believe their visit
has something to do
with this discovery.
- Wait a minute, Professor.
These people are obviously
much more advanced than we are!
What could they
possibly want from us?
- [Reporter] Yes,
they've already achieved
interplanetary space travel,
that's more than we have, sir.
- Ah, it seems
that you are right.
At least about space travel.
In another respect, in
the question of fuel,
their technology
lags far behind ours.
Now, if they were
capable of producing
a rocket fuel like mine,
why, they could
send a hundred ships
to Earth instead of one.
They could conquer the
entire world in a week.
- [Crow] The
Japanese Don Knotts!
- Ah, Jerry, there you are!
- [Servo] Jerry,
baby, ba-bububoom!
- I'm giving you bylines
in the front page!
- [Jerry] Oh, I hope they'll
be someone around to read it!
We've just come
from the war office.
They're declaring
a general alert!
- Oh, a general alert!
- Does it affect my bowtie?
- This must be serious!
- They're gonna
try to land here?
- Well, it's not official,
but they're heading
this way, for sure.
- Is that right?
- They're coming here, then.
- [Servo] You're fascinating!
- Gentlemen, this may be
our last day on Earth.
- [Mike] Let's hit
the karaoke bar.
A rare, Godzilla-free day.
- [Police] This is
Metropolitan Police speaking.
(Servo hums)
All persons are warned
to stay off the streets.
- [Servo] Paging Mr. Herman.
- [Police] Civil
defense personnel,
report to their stations.
Civil defense personnel,
- [Servo] Come on!
- [Police] All
others take shelter.
All other persons take shelter.
Do not panic, follow
instructions, you
will not get hurt.
(Crow hums)
- [Man On Radio] Regional
Control reporting.
All Metropolitan sections
are on red alert.
Repeat, all Metropolitan
sections are on red alert.
Over and out.
- [Servo] Stop looking at
us, mind your own business!
- I wonder where Wally is, he
said he would come tonight.
- [Mike] He's got some
stones to mess with me!
- [Crow] Monet in Paris.
(dog barks)
- [Servo] A woferoo, bohow-wow!
After that dog!
♪ Wheeeere is arfaro ♪
(Mike laughs)
- One minute to eight.
- Is your watch right?
(loud zinging)
- Listen!
Here they come!
- [Crow] Is his watch right?
We may never know.
- Come on!
(loud zinging)
- Can you see anything?
- [Servo] (gasps)
The Sony blimp!
(loud zinging)
- [Man] There, look, over there!
- [Servo] It's cheap trick!
- [Mike] Surrender Dorothy!
- [Servo] Same goes
for you, Paris!
- [Crow] Pagoda of the Damned!
(loud zinging)
- [Servo] An alien race too
proud to ask for directions.
My baby's sunhat and
smock will protect him!
(Mike chuckles)
- [Crow] Protect
me, Japanese Fabian!
(loud zinging)
- Chief!
- What?
- I just got a report
about some strange
electrical disturbance
out in near Beaver Falls.
- You did?
- [Crow] Beaver Falls?
- Oh, let me go,
too, Chief, alright?
- [Servo] Go, you
bizarre little man!
- [Crow] Well, consider
yourself conquered, I gotta go!
("MST3K Love Theme")
- [Man On Radio] Beaver
Falls Control here,
UFO descending in area 220.
- Alright, let's go.
- [Servo] Okay,
uh, yeah, let's go.
(Mike and robots sing)
♪ Oh, here we go off
to Beaver Falls ♪
♪ Beaver Falls ♪
♪ Here we go off
to Beaver Falls ♪
♪ So early in the morning ♪
- [Crow] I burned my tofu!
- Something over there!
- Right.
Maintain radio contact
with headquarters.
- Right.
- [Servo] Oh, the Stanley
Cup has invaded Earth!
Aliens, come here right now!
- No, wait.
- It's a periscope.
- Deploy your men around it!
- Right.
- [Crow] I am the lemon
zester of destruction!
(men talk at the same time)
- Hey, there's Macken's car!
- [Servo] That's a
lot more interesting
than a spaceship, a car!
- [Man] Look, look he's
got his kids with him!
- [Man] Hey, Professor
Macken, you're just in time.
The spaceship just
landed over here.
- Yes, I know.
Well, what's going on,
who's in charge here?
- The Commissioner himself but
he's up there investigating.
(men talk at the same time)
- [Servo] Sir,
your office called.
David Byrne!
Hello!
(chuckles) Hello!
- [Mike] Hello, hello?
- [Crow] What message
speaks the drums?
Junior Samples and Business Boy!
- What's the matter
with you, Mickey?
This might be dangerous!
- I'm not afraid, if
you are, go on home!
- [Servo] Wait, those
are two separate ideas!
- [Crow] (chuckles) Yeah!
(rocket whirring)
- [Servo] What?
- [Crow] It's a
giant watermelon!
Gallagher's taking over!
(robots gasp)
- [Servo] Okay, good luck,
sir, let me know what hap--
Oh, you want me to go with you.
(loud zing)
(men scream loudly)
- [Servo] I saw some
smoke, it's time for lunch,
look at the street.
- Look, it destroyed
them completely!
- [Crow] Except for
their salad bowls!
- [Phantom] Men of Earth,
this is my first warning!
Do not attempt to come near
or you will be destroyed!
Obey my orders, you are warned!
- [Servo] That is one
crafty parking meter!
- Good Lord!
- Get back to the car.
Notify the Defense Ministry!
- Right!
- [Servo] Remember
to crack a window!
Oh hi, Dave, you here, too?
(loud zings)
(men scream)
- [Crow] I'm not afraid, I'm
wearing a tie, you go home!
- Inspector, Inspector!
Where are you, what happened?
Inspector!
- Look, Commissioner,
this is his gun!
- Follow me!
- [Servo] Wet him
if you got him!
- Take cover, it's dangerous!
Radio car, get the
Defense Ministry quick!
- What happened over there?
- Police force was attacked!
Some kind of a death ray!
- [Man] What's that over there?
Look!
(robots gasp)
- Hey, what's that?
- Looks like a flying saucer!
- [Servo] Meh, looks more like
an upside down
flying wheelbarrow
with a stupa on top but I
guess you could think...
(loud zinging)
- [Crow] Oh, it's
Bucky the spaceship!
(loud explosion)
- [Servo] Holy
Santa, pray for us!
Ha, made you duck!
What is that thing, you
go home hats are good?
- [Crow] Hello!
(suspenseful music)
- [Servo] Grown ups of the corn!
Mitch Gaylord.
(Mike laughs)
- What's that, a man?
- Mm-hm.
- [Crow] Believe it or not, yup.
(triumphant music)
- [Servo] The king approacheth!
- Phantom of Krankor,
hear my words!
I warn you to leave this planet.
You are not wanted here.
I warn you for the last time!
- [Servo] And by the
last, I mean first.
(wind blows loudly)
(loud zinging)
- [Crow] I have no powers but
I can skip reasonably well!
- Oh?
- [Masked Man] Your weapons are
useless against me, Phantom!
You are merely exhausting
your energy supply!
You must leave
the Earth at once!
- [Servo] Alright,
let me talk to him.
- Get him on the
televiser, quick!
- [Servo] But I'm
spinning my salad.
- It is enough that I know you.
You are Phantom of Krankor
and you wish to
rule the universe!
- [Crow] He's gonna get
grass stains on his Danskins!
- You are planning now to
destroy the whole world!
I won't let you go
through with this!
You will not get
what you've come for!
You might as well leave now!
- But who are you?
Tell me!
Who are you?
What's your name?
- [Masked Man] I
am Prince of Space!
(robots gasp giddily)
- Wait a moment!
- [Servo] Larry, we got anything
on this Price of Space guy?
(loud ding)
- [Crow] Powered by rotted
fish, I will defeat you!
(loud zinging)
- [Servo] My contacts
is bothering me!
(high pitched whistling)
- Captain, look at
the atom machine!
- The plutonium
is going crazy, sir!
- (laughs) Keep shooting!
You will overload
your power supply!
- [Crow] We have to place
the lunch order, sir.
- He's right!
We'd better quit!
We won't have enough
power to get back!
- Right, we'd
better give up now!
- [Henchman] Shall I
prepare for takeoff, sir?
- [Crow] Make it, ba-caw!
(suspenseful music)
- [Servo] Oh, I can
easily defeat them,
I must get away, Bob!
- Hey, Mickey, let's get
back with the others now.
- Alright.
- And by the way,
you're so fine, hey Mickey.
- They're taking off.
Get them out of here!
Get clear of the rocket blast!
Everybody, get back!
- [Servo] Back to your three
by five apartments, men!
(loud zinging)
A stand of seeders, a
spaceship is taking off,
and I am tired.
It's a haiku! (chuckles)
- [Crow] (chuckles) That's nice!
- [Servo] Oh, thank you!
Into my modified piss helmet!
- Get the emergency
reserve power working!
I'm going to kill
this Prince of Space
if it's the last thing I do!
- [Crow] There goes a norwalf!
- [Mike] So what,
is he escorting them
to the county line?
- [Servo] Mom says I have
to wear this in space
'cause it's cold.
(loud zinging)
- We're ready to shoot, sir.
- Stand by to fire.
- Let him get a little
closer, we can't miss.
- [Crow] He's Prince of
Watching His Space Cushion!
- [Mike] Good spaceship
and a good, close shave.
- [Servo] I gotta turn
on the air, anybody mind?
(loud dings)
- [Crow] 20,000
leagues above the sea.
(loud zinging)
Wow.
In exchange of deadly
negative scratches.
- [Servo] Why don't
we take lunch now?
- He's still coming on.
- [Crow] It's a pretty good war,
but I'm gonna swing it around!
- [Phantom] You there!
Discharge the costing vapors!
- [Mike] Yeah,
look who's talkin'.
- [Servo] Engage
the musical saw!
(eerie music)
- [Crow] It's a
cloud of fish oil!
- [Servo] Is that Ron?
- [Mike] You know, if the
aliens got new spark plugs,
they'd get a lot better miles.
- [Crow] I see that their
ship totally let one!
(loud zinging)
- [Servo] Japanese
are frantically trying
to pick up Singled Out!
Humiliating game shows are
beamed across the nation!
- [Man] Gentlemen, as you are
aware, our national territory
was invaded by an
enemy last night.
- Bingo here!
- He was able
to paralyze our radar
stations and move at will
through our national skies.
It was eventually
driven out single-handed
by the pilot of an
unidentified flying saucer.
- [Servo] Bingo!
- [Man] This pilot calls
himself Prince of Space.
But as to who he is or
where he has come from
or why he's fought our enemy,
we have no information.
We do know, however,
that after the battle,
the flying saucer was seen
returning to this area
and we believe it is
still in this area now.
- Hi!
- Hello, late this morning, huh?
- Last night, what
happened to you?
- Last night?
Oh, an old friend asked
me to go out to dinner.
- Hey, Wally, you missed it.
I saw Prince of
Space last night.
He chased away the spacemen!
- I like that kid.
He's good.
- Here's the whole story,
right here!
You can read it in
this morning's paper.
- Listen, Wally, do you
think that Prince of Space
really comes from a star?
- I guess so.
- Thank you!
- Why not?
What do you think?
The Prince of Space might
just be a man like Wally?
- [Crow] Woody
Allen asked me out.
- [Wally] In a way he is,
if you think about it.
After all, I believe
in peace, too.
I'd be willing to fight
this Phantom character,
same way as he did.
- [Mickey] Ha-ha, you
wouldn't fight him!
You're too scared!
- [Servo] Are we gonna
work at all today?
- [Wally] Going where?
- [Mickey] Over to
Johnnie's house.
- [Mike] Let's get outta here.
- [Crow] Let's go
to Johnnie's house.
I like it very much!
(doors close)
- Oh yeah, Mike, I was
wondering that myself.
Weird, isn't it?
- Oh hey, Tom--
How'd you get here so fast?
- Oh, he'll be along. (laughs)
I have his chicken puppet!
- Hey, where's Crow?
- Talking like what?
- Why are you talking like that?
- No, I'm not, I'm just
way ahead of you, Mike!
- Well, like that, you're
answering my questions
before I ask 'em.
I don't know, I'm just
asking him the same thing.
- No, you dope!
I mean I'm moving faster
than you temporally speaking!
- Hey, what do you mean
you're way ahead of me?
- Well, I asked you for it,
Crow, you were right here!
- Hi, guys!
Hey, how'd you get here so fast?
- That's what I've been
trying to tell you, Mike!
I'm ahead of you by
about three seconds!
- You know what, guys?
I think there may
be something wrong
with the space-time continuum?
- Servo, how'd you
get my chicken puppet?
- Woof, sorry!
Everything's on the fritz!
My burrito was done before
I put it in the oven!
- Alright, alright, take
your damn chicken puppet!
I'll have it back before
you know it anyway! (laughs)
- Okay, Tom, why don't you just
give him his chicken puppet
back, alright?
- Say, why don't
we ask Gypsy to mess
with the warp engine?
- Well's all I know is I
want my chicken puppet back!
Hey, how'd that happen?
- That's a good idea.
Gypsy, there's something wrong
with the space-time thingie.
Isn't there anything we can do?
- Well, okay, Gypsy, I guess
all we can do is ride it out.
I'm outta here.
- Okay, Gypsy, I guess all
we can do is ride it out.
I'm g--
Wow, that's a weird déjà vu.
(Tom laughs)
Yeah, that's a good
idea, Crow, you do that.
This is really weird.
We'll be right back.
- Well, I'm just gonna
play with my chicken puppet
till this blows over.
I'll see you, Mike!
Tom! (whistles)
(loud zinging)
Hey, anybody seen
my chicken puppet?
("MST3K Love Theme")
- [Servo] Sugar,
nature's rich bounty,
helping the war effort!
- [Mike] Still lagging
behind, Crow, huh?
- [Crow] Shut up.
You know, a "scare me" would
really help things out here.
(chuckles) "Scare me".
- [Servo] It's a Sealy
Posture-Pedic cornfield!
- [Crow] All those
Heaven's Gate people
were supposed to meet us here.
(suspenseful music)
- [Servo] We have to
chop the (mumbles)
and then get to the invasion!
- [Mike] Today's lotto
numbers are seven.
- Careful now.
This microwave search will
help us locate that Prince.
- Mm-hm.
- We'll find him.
That miserable scum.
- He stole my cup!
(Mike laughs)
- When I find him, I'm
gonna kill him myself!
- [Servo] Uh, I was actually
signed up to do that, sir.
- Oh, here he is!
- [Henchman] Location
four and a half miles
northwest of here.
(mumbles) 37.2, inside
a concrete building.
Strong iron reaction.
- Can I move this thing,
thanks.
- Hmm, that puts him
near Macken's laboratory!
Hey!
See if you can get
him on the telefinder!
(Servo hums Pop Goes the Weasel)
- [Servo] Luxury
retirement compounds!
- Right over there, sir!
- Mm-hm.
- [Crow] Well, I'm back from
break, anything shaking?
- Let's go get 'em!
Break out the underground tank!
- [Servo] Round the
underpants for a change!
- [Henchman]
Attention, below there!
Prepare the underground tank!
Coordinate 602--
- Oh, oh, oh.
- [Mike] What gets into
some civilizations?
- I don't know.
- Pretty small cubicles!
- [Johnnie] I've been watching
all morning, but it's no use!
- [Mickey] Why not?
- [Johnnie] I think he
only comes around at night!
- [Mickey] Why?
- He's evil and evil people
always come around at night!
- Nobody's watching, they
even come in the daytime.
- [Crow] Although, when
evil people are mating,
they will appear
at dawn sometimes.
(suspicious music)
- I'm Hard Rock.
- I'm Coco.
- I'm Joe.
- Hey, look!
There's some funny people!
They're crawling out of a hole!
- Really, give me that!
- Abner, come look!
- [Crow] Do we all have to go?
What are we, a bunch of women?
- Hey, that looks
like that space man.
Remember the other night?
- You're right!
We'll go see, come on!
- [Servo] I have a trial
at three, let's go!
- Take these, will you?
- Wait!
Where are you going now?
- We're gonna spy
on those space men!
They're in the old factory!
- What?!
(suspenseful music)
- [Crow] We filled
out pants, sir!
(Tom and Mike laugh)
- [Servo] Ready and mince,
mince, mince, mince,
mince, mince, mince....
- [Crow] Wait, this
isn't where we parked--
Oh yeah, upper level, come on.
- [Servo] The Caped
Caplain Brigade!
Aha, and now the real
reason we came here!
Refurbishing old
buildings and selling them
as affordable condominiums!
(Prince laughs)
- [Crow] Raceway park!
- You came.
I've been expecting you!
- I came, yes.
(Prince laughs)
And now I'm going to kill you!
- Ha-ha! Oh--
- Just how
do you propose to do that?
Your ray guns will have no
effect on me or my ship!
I've told you that already.
- Hold on,
I'm gettin' a
Dodger's game here.
- You'd better leave
this planet in peace.
I warned you once before.
- Kill him!
(loud zing)
(loud explosion)
- [Crow] Come on, little buddy!
- Where did he go?
- He disappeared!
- No, in here, he must be here!
(Tom pants heavily)
- He's gone.
- The coward, he ran away.
- Looking for me?
- Uh, yeah we are,
hi!
- I'm not running away.
No, I wanna stay because
I'm gonna prevent you
from getting Dr.
Macken's formula!
- Kill him!
- Would you guys just listen?
Your guns don't work! (sighs)
- Some of you
go that way!
- Aagh!
- Aaagh!
- Bring the laser cannon!
- The Prince is there!
- Yeah, he must be fighting
with that Phantom!
- [Crow] Somebody left a
perfectly good refrigerator
over there! (laughs)
- [Henchman] Here's
the laser cannon, sir.
- Good.
- [Henchman] We
can't find him, sir!
- Listen!
Show yourself!
Otherwise we're gonna
kill some different!
- Some different?
- Different?
- [Prince] I hear you!
Come in here!
I'm waiting for you!
Leave the children alone!
- [Crow] You hear
that, Jerry Seinfeld?
- [Prince] You cannot harm them
anyway as long as I am here!
- [Mike] Do you need a ladder?
- I've got you now, you scum!
(Mike and robots laugh)
- Scum?
- [Servo] Where'd
that come from?
- This is the end for you!
- Ya jerk!
- You'll be a horrible example
for anyone who opposes me!
- [Servo] Really
horrible example
because no one else will
ever be scared of him.
(loud zinging)
- (laughs) I told you.
Your weapons have
no effect on me!
- [Servo] It is my
considerate advice
that you discontinue your
use of said weapon! Ha-ha!
(Phantom shouts)
- See, you are scum!
(Mike laughs)
- [Mike] I'll throw
my doll at you!
- Let's go!
(dramatic music)
- [Servo] Tiniwee-yuway!
- Hey wait, you go that way!
(children shout)
(Mike and robots laugh)
- [Crow] You know, this is where
your cram school experience
really comes in handy!
We have to get back
to bootblacking, we
like it very much!
- Please, don't let
him take me, please!
- [Servo] Empirical data
suggests the accuracy
of my earlier contention
that your weapons against
me are without merit!
- [Crow] Ooh, ouchie, ouchie,
ouchie, ouchie, ooh, ow, ooh!
- You're a good shot!
(dramatic music)
- [Servo] Oof, my lumbar!
- Oh!
(Crow laughs)
- Come here!
- Help, help, Prince, help me!
- [Crow] Again,
detention is thwarted.
- [Servo] Please,
call me the artist!
- Did you get hurt?
Are you both alright?
- Yes, Prince!
Oh boy, you beat up that
Phantom pretty good!
- Yes.
Don't wanna kill him though.
Listen, the police are
coming, we'd better go now.
- Right.
(sirens wail faintly)
- [Servo] It's so chilly
I brought my shawl.
- Johnnie, listen to me.
I wanna give you something.
Keep it with you always.
If you ever need me again,
just turn the dial, understand?
- I'll turn the dial!
- [Servo] If you need me!
- You won't tell
anybody about this.
Agreed?
- Yes.
- Alright, goodbye now.
- [Crow] (chuckles) Who we
gonna tell first? (chuckles)
- Hey, there's the Commissioner!
- [Servo] Pete Rosseau?
(footsteps echo loudly)
- [Mike] (chuckles)
Wow, tap dogs!
- Look, there's the
kid! Hey, Mickey!
- Commissioner!
- Well, what's going on?
- The Prince of Space and
Phantom, they were fighting!
- Phantom got beat
up and ran away!
- What'd you say?
The Prince of Space?
(Crow laughs)
- The one who has
the flying saucer.
- Yeah!
- The one you saw last night?
- Yeah, that's right!
- And he was here today?
- Yeah! Right, Johnnie?
- Mm-hm!
- Good job not telling, kids!
- He even spoke with us,
you know what he said?
- Yeah, he said the space
men came here to Earth
(mumbles) the Mackens'
new rocket fuel.
- [Servo] Yeah, the big
goomba's gonna take the fuel!
- [Policeman] Look at this!
- [Crow] Terry got my gun dirty!
- One of those space
men was using that!
- One of those space men?
- Chief!
- The building is empty!
- They all got away, huh?
Come on, your father's
worried about you.
- Alright.
- Take over.
- [Servo] Yeah, right, whatever.
- [Crow] Wow, it's a really
modern Lutheran Church!
- [Servo] They're
gonna pop in here
for some sushi burritos.
- [Johnnie] Dr. Sangamon!
- [Doctor] What is it, boys?
- Please, sir.
Are you going to go
ahead with the tests?
- Of course we are.
- Everything's ready, doctor.
- Good.
- You can run
a swab out the
particle accelerator?
- Oh listen, boys.
I
think you'd be
better off at home.
There's no danger, of course,
but we don't want
any chances, right?
- If this Phantom shows up,
these soldiers aren't
gonna be much good.
- Yeah.
I wish Prince of Space
was here with us.
- Did you bring
the die with you?
- Why, sure.
- Why don't we call him with it?
Then we're not in
any trouble, really,
but we don't wanna
take any chances.
- [Crow] What the hell
happened to my pants?
- I'm gonna tell him
it was your idea.
- Mm-hm.
- [Servo] So if we get
busted, it's your ass!
(kids shout)
You're a handsome woman.
- Lawrence, what was that noise?
- [Lawrence] Did
you hear a noise?
- Mm-hm.
- [Lawrence] I only
hear the turbines.
- I see.
- Look, it's him, the Phantom!
- Ha-ha, the little
troublemakers, huh?
- [Mike] When chickens attack!
(kids shout in pain)
("MST3K Love Theme")
- Goodbye.
- I'm retiring
and moving to Florida!
- Well, this is a
great day for us!
- [Servo] Jimmy Osmond!
(dramatic music)
(loud zinging)
- The day is less great now!
- No! (screams)
- [Servo] For some reason,
that doesn't work on hats!
- [Professor] Who are you,
what do you want?
- You know what I want!
Your rocket fuel.
Those soldiers who
are standing there
are good examples of what my
ray guns can do, Professor.
So don't try my patience!
- But do try
my homemade griddle cakes.
- Well, are you going to
talk or do you want me
to start with the children?
- There's a safe right here!
- Get moving!
- [Crow] I thought you
said you were gonna start
with the (chuckles) children!
- Mars, puts guards on the door.
- Yes, sir.
- Mars?
(kids shout)
- [Crow] Didn't they
consider taking over
one of the Earth's good nations?
- Well, what are
you waiting for?
I want that safe opened!
- [Mike] Oh, sorry,
I'm a little out of it.
I stayed up and watched
Letterman last night.
(triumphant music)
Please, mister!
Cram school at three a.m.!
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] If I can only
reach this dried squid!
- [Servo] Oh, the
secret armoire!
- [Crow] Whoops, my doorknob!
- [Phantom] Ha,
this is what I want!
- [Servo] The abstracted
deed and your late crappity!
(kids shout indistinctly)
Give me that remote!
- Help us, Prince!
- Prince!
- [Servo] Allow me to
reference my earlier codicil
on how your weapons
are ineffective!
- Enough!
There's no use firing.
Your guns won't work against me!
- [Crow] Have I mentioned that?
- And Phantom, give the
bag back to the Doctor.
- [Servo] Argh, what
a bunch of crap.
- Take him!
(henchmen shout)
- Prince!
- [Crow] They all
have me goiters.
(henchmen shout)
- Prince, you saved us!
- Stand clear, boys.
- Move on, Johnnie,
you're going with me!
- Prince, help!
- One move, he'll die!
- No! Let the boy go!
Take the formula!
Let the boy go!
- [Servo] So, am I your hostage?
Should I--
Oh,
(loud explosion)
(soldiers shout)
Aha! I guess.
- [Crow] Medical Center,
starring Evel Knievel!
(sirens wail)
- [Servo] They were
supposed to meet me
here in the saucer!
- [Crow] Air Krankor!
(loud zing)
(loud explosion)
- [Servo] Oh, Krankor blew
up a potential tackler
in the 40 and now there's
nothing but daylight!
Their invasion is like
poorly planned bank heist!
- [Crow] (chuckles) You
just opened up a whole can
of jellied whoop ass, pal!
- [Mike] You know,
I'll never go by
a switching station without
thinking of this scene.
(loud zing)
(loud explosion)
- [Crow] Your guns are useless
but scare the crap
out of me anyway!
- [Servo] There's trouble
at the church of the bomb!
(loud zing)
(loud explosion)
- Oh!
- [Crow] So, you gonna let me
invade your planet now, huh?
Huh?
- No, not that, don't touch--
- [Servo] You can't use the
phone, it doesn't dial out!
- Don't touch it!
Help!
- [Mike] The easily
bamboozled Prince of Space.
- [Servo] Meanwhile in
a carwash in Yokahama.
(suspenseful music)
(loud blast)
- Alright, that's fine,
it's fine, we got
fire insurance!
It's alright!
- [Servo] Never even
had time to tell Houston
that they had a problem.
Oh, the inanity!
- [Crow] Oh, the
Japan-ity! (chuckles)
(siren wails)
- Aww, that's a shame!
- Dr. Macken! Dr. Macken!
How horrible!
He blew up the ship!
Look, there they go now!
- [Servo] People looking
very Spielberg-ian!
- Oh! The Prince of Space!
He's going after them!
(loud zinging)
- [Crow] Yes, I
am Prince of Space
and I am going after them!
- [Servo] And his
companion, Duke of Puddles!
(loud zinging)
He sent us some cinnamon rolls!
There's the icing and the dough
is usually under the icing.
Here.
Okay, let's see here!
Dear Japan, bite me.
Love, Prince of Space!
- I will bring back
the formula after I chase
these invaders home.
Signed, Prince of Space.
- [Crow] In the
meantime, there may be
many more horrible deaths.
Um, Torva?
- [Pilot] Your
attention, please.
You're in our flight
from San Francisco
will land at International
Airport in 15 minutes.
Please observe the no
smoking sign when it is lit.
Thank you.
- [Servo] Man, what an ugly
bunch of kids, they yours?
- Doctor, I think you
dropped this photograph.
- Oh, thank you!
- That's your sister, isn't it?
She'd never forgive
you if you lost it.
- [Servo] Yeah, uh, don't
talk to me anymore, alright?
(loud zinging)
- A giant roast turkey!
- [Servo] Do you
want the window seat?
(suspenseful music)
Hey, that lady
got extra peanuts!
- [Crow] And she got
the whole can, too!
(hums a cheerful tune)
- You want me, sir?
- [Chief] Ah, Captain
Munakata, come in, please.
- [Servo] I understand
you're stuffed with cheese.
- I want you to investigate
the disappearance
of a civilian aircraft,
you understand?
- Yes, sir.
- [Man] About 10 minutes ago,
our radio contact with
the plane was interrupted.
- [Crow] Who's
talking? (chuckles)
- [Man] At the time,
it must have been
approaching--
- Are we hearing voices?
- Point Barrow?
- We believe so.
- [Munakata] I'll
go, immediately.
- [Servo] Or Thursday.
- Munakata.
Be careful.
- Yes, sir, I will.
- Love you!
(loud zoom)
- [Munakata] Baker tower
from dog charlie 22,
come in.
- Woof, over.
- [Man In Radio] Baker
tower here, go ahead.
- [Munakata] Altitude 10,000
feet, Point Barrow dead ahead.
Nothing in view.
Will circle and
investigate, over.
- [Man In Radio]
Roger, over and out.
- [Crow] I'm a wasp, over. Bzzt!
(loud zoom)
- [Servo] Hey,
it's Stevie Wonder!
♪ Isn't she lovely ♪
♪ Isn't she wonderful ♪
(shouts in pain)
(Mike and robots laugh)
- [Munakata] Baker tower!
Baker tower!
I can't move!
I--
- [Servo] Wait,
sorry, I can move!
I just forgot how for a second!
- Dog charlie!
Dog charlie!
What's the matter?
Hello, dog charlie!
Come in, please!
What's the matter?
Can you read me?
- [Munakata] I can't move!
My instruments!
My instruments
are going haywire!
- [Mike] My violin,
my tuba, haywire!
- What's the matter?
- [Munakata]
Controls are locked!
- Munakata, what's the matter?
- [Crow] This!
This is the matter!
(loud zinging)
- [Servo] The pilot is teething!
- [Munakata] A dragon ship!
A black dragon!
- What?
- [Servo] What do you mean what?
- Munakata, what did you say?
(Munakata shouts)
- [Crow] I hit my
knee on the dashboard!
Wow! Hurts!
- [Servo] There is dog
hair all over the car!
Why do you think that is, hm?
- Oh, good evening, Professor!
- [Professor] Good evening!
- And then all the notes
that you asked me to take
at the conference last week.
I'm sure you'll find
everything in order, Doctor.
- Oh, if you did
it, I'm sure I will!
- Thank you, sir.
- Hey, Dad, Dad, wait!
Wait, Dad!
- Secretary of children.
- Oh, John!
Did you have a good
day at school, son?
- Yes, I did.
I wanted to talk to you.
Where are you going?
- To the Defense Ministry.
- Will you be back soon?
- [Servo] No,
because I loathe you!
- Not before your
bedtime, I'm afraid.
- Aww gee, Dad.
I want to talk to you!
About these invaders
from outer space.
- [Crow] He's putting
his cigarette out on him!
Ow!
- Well, let's talk about
it tomorrow morning
at breakfast, huh?
- [Crow] Um, how come
you're so old, Dad?
Did you have me when you
were like 60 or something?
- Oh, I'm afraid I'm a bit
late for this conference.
Major Murkey will be worried.
Will you call him and
tell him I'm on my way?
- Certainly, goodbye, Doctor!
- Bye, Dad!
And don't forget our theory!
- [Servo] Goodbye, people I
seem to share a house with!
(engine growls)
- [Crow] Goodbye.
- I'm sorry, Dr. Macken
has not yet arrived.
- But, Major, what could
have happened to him?
It's not like Macken at all
to be this late
for an appointment.
- Gentlemen, I'm quite
alarmed about this.
Dr. Macken may be in trouble.
In any case, we can do
nothing without him.
At least may be able to
determine his whereabouts.
Major Murkey,
with your permission--
- Murky?
- This matter immediately.
- Very good, Captain.
Go ahead.
Gentlemen, I suggest
a half hour recess--
- Recess!
- Woohoo!
(wind howls)
- Wow!
The Earth is so smooth, it
must have been dermabrasioned!
(wind howls)
- [Crow] Sounds like the
Earth needs new break pads.
See how things are goin'.
- [Mike] Okay,
we'll check it out.
("MST3K Love Theme")
- Yep, seems like it doesn't it?
- So you think we're back in
sync on the whole time thing?
(Tom chuckles)
- D'oh!
- Oh, I'm sorry, sorry--
- Okay, hey guys, listen up.
I think I have some answers.
Apparently, the
separate universe layers
are co-mingling.
(Tom laughs)
If we don't isolate our
position in space and time,
(robots laugh)
limitless potential--
What?
- Mike, you're a small robot!
- Yeah!
- (laughs) Of course, I am!
What do you expect?
- Well, normally when we're
not in a wormhole and stuff,
you're a big,
chunky human thing!
- Well, I don't mean to
offend you or anything
but as you are, I have
the urge to put you back
in your cage!
(robots laugh)
- C'mon, cut it out.
Now, I can't speak for
your reality but in mine,
we are all robots serving on
this vessel and I'm in command.
You have tremendous
respect for me!
You do!
Now my orders are as follows.
I want you--
- Sorry, Mike.
I only take orders
from Willy Tyler
and Lester Hog!
- Oho, good one!
(robots laugh)
- Oh, that's--
Stop, now come on, stop!
Now stop it!
Now listen up!
We all wanna get back right?
- Yes.
- Okay, listen up.
If we wanna put things right,
you'll do just as I say.
If we can overdrive
the plasma thrusters
to create a gravity well,
isolating us from the
other universe layers,
we untangle our co-mingling--
(robots laugh loudly)
- He's so cute!
- Come on, cut it out!
You guys are gonna be
annihilated and stuff!
- Oh, Mike, I don't care, man!
It's worth it to
see you like this!
- No, stop it!
(loud buzzing)
(Mike and robots
shout indistinctly)
- [Mike] Don't push, don't
push, don't push, don't push!
(doors open loudly)
- [Crow] Come on,
move it, Short Stuff!
- [Mike] I'm movin', I'm
movin', don't push, I'm fine.
- [Crow] It says
employees must wash hands
before returning to invasion!
(Mike chuckles)
- [Mike] (gasps) A
mummified Alf Landon!
- [Servo] Good morning, honey!
- Professor Macken.
Welcome aboard.
- Who, who are you?
- Come, come, Professor!
Permit me to introduce myself!
They call me Phantom
of Krankor.
But you seem
startled, Professor.
Sit down, relax.
- [Crow] Hey, Z-7, suck it in!
- Is this a dream?
Where am I?
- You want to know
where you are?
- [Servo] No, I
wanna know (mumbles).
Of course I wanna
know where I am!
- Aboard my flagship.
Halfway between your
world and Krankor.
- [Professor] How did
you bring me here?
- For a man of
your intelligence,
a full explanation
would be necessary.
But we have no time
for that, Professor.
- But what about my chauffer?
- Come now, my dear Professor,
what a silly question!
Do you expect me to keep track
of your worthless servants?
We blasted him
out of an airlock,
so by now he may have fallen
into a star! (laughs evilly)
- [Servo] Wow,
that guy's nuttier
than a Stuckey's log.
- Well, I suppose
that you expect me to help
you with your evil plans!
- [Crow] Yeah, would you mind?
Thanks!
- That is precisely
why I gave orders
to take you aboard.
I will show you much here
that only you can appreciate.
For example how I propose
to control the universe!
When you've seen all this,
you will realize
how futile it is
for you or anyone
else to oppose me!
- [Servo] Fine, just
go light on the probes!
(loud zinging)
Making no progress at all.
- [Crow] It's incredible
how accurate this is
at depicting space!
♪ Some people call me
Space Cowboy, yeah ♪
- Hey!
Look at that!
- [Mike] Oh, oh, I'm
sorry, I got distracted.
- Oh!
- [Crow] There's the kids'
playroom and we're gonna--
- Hey, Chief, we got
that flying saucer
on the televisers.
Coming up fast at stern!
- What?
- [Servo] What?
- Get him back to his
quarters under guard!
- [Henchman] Right, sir.
Come on, you.
- [Mike] Oh, speed! Oh!
- Come on, I said!
- [Crow] It's the
instant miso soup bower!
(Mike hums Pop Goes the Weasel)
- Eh, it's him alright.
- [Mike] Saying it is me
will have no effect on me.
(loud whooshing)
- [Crow] It's a flying
rotary nose hair clipper!
- I've got him right
where I want him!
- [Servo] Somewhere in space!
- [Mike] Don't look at my butt!
- Now he dies!
- [Crow] Just wanna test
some batteries here first!
(loud zinging)
- [Servo] Aha, and they
stay crunchy in milk, hmm!
- [Mike] Swing me over
there, trusty string!
- [Crow] He's in
the wiener mobile!
(loud zinging)
- [Servo] Oh no, he lost
control of his fried egg!
- Enough.
He's finished.
- [Mike] Look at that.
- [Servo] Oh! No, don't!
(evil laugh)
- [Mike] I have to tell
Fang about that! Ha!
(loud zing)
- They're landing
on Captain Picard's head!
- [Servo] Oh, it's a planet
where sea monkeys come from!
(Mike chuckles)
(loud zing)
- [Crow] Whoa! Look at that!
Look at that!
- [Servo] It's a trip
to Mike's subconscious!
- [Mike] It's pretty
accurate, I gotta admit.
- [Crow] It's a DQ planet!
(loud zing)
(loud whir)
- [Servo] Dress to
the right stuff!
- Chafe, chafe,
chafe, chafe, chafe.
- Shall I put Macken
with the others?
- Of course not.
Bring him to the great hall.
- Right, sir.
- And prepare to
return to Earth.
- Right, sir!
- [Mike] Uh, didn't we just
get back from Earth, sir?
- [Servo] Sir, do
we have a plan or--
- [Crow] So, crack corn
all around then, gentlemen?
- I've a special job for you!
- Yes, sir!
- I want you to find
that Prince of Space.
- Prince of Space?
- You heard me right.
He may have possibly
escaped destruction
when we passed through
that meteorite shower.
- [Servo] Prince of Space, sir?
- I must have positive
proof that he's finished.
He may make some foolish
attempt to rescue our prisoners
and disrupt my
plans for the Earth.
- [Mike] Uh, sir,
I was gonna ask you
if I should bring this
to the lab, don't! Oh!
- The last we saw of his ship,
it was falling
away toward Earth.
He may possibly have been
able to return to his base!
- [Crow] Prince of Space?
- [Henchman] Of course, he
must have a base somewhere!
- That's right.
He must have one there
and I want you to find it.
- I'll find it alright.
I can promise you that!
- You'd better take
the X-radar with you
to help you find him!
He sure will give you the
formula for his wavelength.
You.
- Fight me!
- Accompany him!
- Right, sir!
- Install the X-radar in
one of the ground cars
of the Earthlings and
comb the city for him!
(Mike and robots snicker)
He's bound to be
disguised, of course.
Perhaps as a civilian.
But if it's properly set up,
the X-radar will
find him easily!
And when you find
him, report to me!
And above all,
keep track of him.
I prefer to deal
personally with him.
And if you don't find him,
don't bother to come back!
- [Henchmen] Right, sir!
We go to obey your orders!
- Dismissed!
- [Servo] First, we have
to go to the bathroom!
(loud buzz)
- Professor Macken is waiting
for you in the great hall!
- [Crow] Always quarter to
three here at Krankor's place!
- Good.
You.
Bring in the others and
put 'em up on the stage.
- Yes, sir.
- I'm ashamed of my talk show.
(Mike laughs)
- [Crow] Great hall designed
by the Lego Corporation!
- [Servo] Well, we don't
have as big a turnout
as we expected tonight so if
you could all just move down
to the first few rows...
- At ease, men.
- I mean, man.
- Professor Macken.
- (snorts) Oh, ah, oh!
- I want to bid you welcome
to the planet of Krankor!
And to my home.
You must have seen a lot from
the window of my flagship.
The castle cut from
the living rock.
My giant guardian and so forth.
I have many more
wonders to show you.
And I've even brought
some friends of yours
to share this
experience with you!
- [Crow] Can I get more
coffee over here, please?
- [Servo] Pork and Mr. Moonies.
- [Mike] All my roadie friends!
- Dr. Fletcher!
- Oh!
Macken!
- [Crow] I'm scared!
- Are you alright?
- Oh, Professor!
- [Mike] I forgot to
water your plants!
- [Mike And Robots] Lucille!
- Dr. Cummings!
- [Dr. Fletcher] Yes, and
this is Professor Coin.
- Lucille.
- Oh, I'm so sorry
about this, Dr. Cummings.
- [Dr. Fletcher] And
here is Professor Goriets
from Southern Institute.
- Lucille.
- Oh.
- [Servo] Mrs. Karma Goat.
- [Phantom] Gentlemen,
we have much to discuss!
Please sit down!
- [Crow] Please.
No, really, please!
Sit down!
- [Servo] So
they're alien except
for their Chippendale furniture.
- [Mike] Sorry, I'm late, cat
threw up this morning, hi.
- Very good.
- You sit well!
- Everyone I need
seems to be here.
I appreciate your
coming, gentlemen.
I'm honored to find
myself in the company
of five of the most
advanced minds of Earth.
Please make yourselves
comfortable.
- Until they arrive.
- While I explain my plans.
Plans in which you gentlemen
play a very important part.
(laughs evilly)
- I have to leave early.
- [Doctor] You can't!
This is impossible!
- Be silent.
I am dictator of Krankor.
I assure you
that the word impossible
is a word, which for
me, does not exist.
- [Crow] Although
I just said it.
- [Phantom] Now, first
of all, Professor Macken.
I've arranged an
interesting show for you.
I trust that you will
find it quite instructive!
Go ahead.
(Tom hums loudly)
- [Mike] Lean forward.
- Why, that--
Why, that's my house!
- So it is.
You are quite right,
Professor Macken.
Your house.
- [Servo] You win this round.
- And it's half a million
Earth miles from here.
- [Mike] But it's
on the bus line...
- Oh!
Johnnie!
- [Crow] The slammed
the iron gate on me
at cram school again today!
(melancholy music)
- [Servo] Samuel Barbers' adagio
for young Japanese children.
- [Mike] (chuckles) That's cold.
- [Crow] Well, I'm
sure this little scene
is leading somewhere if
you'll all be patient.
- [Servo] Now watch as we
turn the lawn sprinklers
on our little Johnnie!
- [Mike] Here's the
Japanese Suzanne Pleshette.
(loud zinging)
- [Crow] Jeez, my
life is really boring!
- [Phantom] Well, gentlemen,
what do you think of that?
- [Servo] What?
I just got better.
- [Phantom] Nothing you do on
Earth can be hidden from me!
I've watched all of
your secrets from here!
You see, I've been watching
you for a long time now.
- [Mike] He knows
about the porn.
- [Phantom] And I knew
right where to find you
when I wanted to.
- [Crow] So you
know about my rash?!
- That's an impressive
toy but first of all,
I demand to know why
you brought us here!
- [Servo] Grab some bed, flumpy!
- You demand nothing.
You will merely obey
my instructions.
Take your place
and remain silent
while I explain why
you were brought here.
You five men are among the
top scientists of Earth.
Your governments
respect your opinions,
thus, you men are well
equipped to evaluate my power!
You know I can exterminate
the world any time I want to.
I want you to explain
this to your people.
Impress upon them how useless
it would be to oppose me!
You will tell them I
demand their surrender.
You.
- Bite me!
- You, each and
every one of you!
- Bite me!
- No! I won't!
It's out of the question!
I won't!
I will never betray my people!
- I refuse categorically--
- No, I will never
be your tool!
- [Doctor] None of us will!
- Agreed!
- Of course we agree!
- [Servo] I'll do it!
- Apparently you
gentlemen are upset.
I will give you a
chance to think it over.
Calmly.
After all you are
men of science.
We are leaving to attack
your world in 12 hours.
- What's he going to do?
- With your cooperation
or without it,
I'm going to attack.
I shall destroy one of
your major cities first.
Afterward, I'm sure
you will cooperate.
(laughs evilly)
- [Servo] Starts with the
United (mumbles) is it?
- [Mike] No.
- [Crow] The young one ship.
(loud zing)
It's kinda hard to
go into warp drive
when you're burnin' so much oil.
- Professor, may I?
- Thank you.
- You must eat something!
Do you feel alright?
- [Servo] Don't light a
match is all I'll say!
- The poor man suffers so.
- [Crow] I'm from
the 19th century,
what does he want with me?
- [Mike] Bad news, all
out of curly fries.
- The Chief wants you.
- [Mike] In the worst way!
- [Professor] We were just
about to begin eating.
- You eat later.
- And me.
- What's the matter?
Isn't our food good
enough for you?
Come on, hurry up with you!
- [Professor] The man is sick!
Leave him alone!
- On your feet, you!
- But he's a sick man!
- Get away!
- [Crow] Oh, he waved
his stinky foot at me!
- [Henchman] Come on, eat this!
Eat it, I tell you!
- [Mike] Ah, Mr. Bond.
- Ah, good morning, gentlemen.
You slept well, I hope.
- [Servo] Yes, in
my double-breasted
sleeping suit and tie.
- [Mike] Tell Mom
we're about to eat.
- [Doctor] Listen.
I speak for my colleagues
as well as myself.
It is impossible to
agree to your demands.
- What?
- [Doctor] We are
only men of science.
We can explain to our people
the state of your technology.
But we cannot accept
responsibility
for making political decisions.
- [Crow] Who's talking?
(Mike chuckles)
- Again!
- I cannot comprehend
the civilization
where intelligent
men like yourselves
are not permitted to guide
the destinies of their people.
Very well then.
You agree to describe
our technology.
And you will do it so well
that even your government heads
will realize the
hopelessness of opposing me.
- [Servo] Alrighty then.
- You'll make the
necessary arrangements then
to send us back to Earth?
- [Phantom] No need of that.
You can broadcast your
message directly from here.
- That means that we--
- That's right!
You may expect to remain
with us for some time.
Until you have assisted
me with all my plans.
- [Crow] Bryce, when will
I see you again, Bryce?
(sinister music)
- [Mike] I'm gonna
mess you up, boom!
- [Servo] Beautiful,
just beautiful.
(suspenseful music)
Like a brainy green of Japan.
Is this just a really
slow chase scene?
With one car?
- [Crow] What, are we driving
through plutonium or--
- [Mike] It's Garbo.
- Hey! Wake up!
Be careful.
I don't think the
Chief would like it
if he knew you were
sleeping on the job!
- [Mike] Hey, wake up,
your egg is hatching.
- What is it?
- That's better.
You heard anything
from the flagship?
From the Chief?
- Not since they passed
through the meteor zone.
- Alright, stay awake!
- [Crow] Yeah, blow
it out your gizzard.
- Nothing new.
We'd better get some kind
of a lead on that Prince
before the Chief gets here.
- Sure is funny how he
disappeared without a trace.
His car, too.
- Get outta the way!
- I know, but they
don't know anything!
- The Commissioner
told me they figure
it must have been the space men.
- I guess so.
- It's the only explanation.
- [Crow] My Slurpee spilled!
- Pick up something?
(Tom hums Pop Goes the Weasel)
- Okay, right foot.
- [Man With Newspaper]
Don't work so fast.
(suspenseful music)
- [Crow] Are you ever
gonna stop farting?
Is that even a
remote possibility?
- That's close enough.
Cut in the automatic search.
(Tom hums Pop Goes the Weasel)
- [Servo] Well, no more guns
shelled again last night.
(suspenseful music)
Get back to work or you're
back out on the street!
- It's the shoeshine boy.
- Put it on the beam.
- Right.
(loud buzzing)
Attention, X-radar get
very high reading of 98
on shoeshine boy.
- [Phantom] Tune it in properly!
- [Mike] Just wiggle it around!
- [Servo] Check, please.
(sirens wailing)
Would you mind
if I paid you in TicTacs?
- (chuckles) So our Prince
of Space is disguised
as a miserable bootblack.
Clever.
We never would have picked
him up without the X-radar.
Attention, Earth Patrol.
This is your Commander
speaking personally to you.
Now that you have found
this Prince of Space,
be careful and keep him
in sight at all times.
- [Crow] Careful!
He'll try to sell you
shoelaces with your shine!
- You heard what he said.
- [Servo] Yeah, whatever.
- [Mike] Can I
just learn to read
and then I'll come back to work?
- [Crow] I got a bootblack
down at the track,
yup, big bootblacking
thing goin' on.
- [Servo] Hey, bootblack,
congratulations!
What did you do?
- Mr. Tannen!
Hey, Mr. Tannen!
- Get out of my wine!
- You forgot this.
You're getting absentminded.
- [Crow] Be healed!
(chuckles) Man, I
hate that bastard.
- [Mike] You carry
Bootblack Journal?
No?
- [Crow] Ah, here it is!
Little Baby Sunhats
Monthly! (chuckles)
- Scalpel.
- What happened?
- He ran away.
- He came back.
It's alright now.
- No, wait.
He ran away again.
- [Phantom] Attention,
Earth Patrol, attention.
We will arrive over
the city in 30 seconds.
- [Crow] We better
clean this place up!
- Report any suspicious
movements when we
appear in the sky.
- [Servo] I had a suspicious
moment after breakfast!
- [Henchman] Full
descent to 500 feet.
- [Crow] Set whole
friers to stun!
(loud zing)
- [Servo] The upper half
of a Hopper painting.
(people shout)
Oh! A giant roast chicken!
- [Crow] It is brown
on the outside,
tender and juicy on the inside!
- [Mike] It is not fermented
pickle or raw, wrong!
- [Crow] Potatoes are stuffing!
(people shout)
♪ When I was Japanese,
it was a very good year ♪
- [Crow] Oh!
Ice dams!
We have ice dams!
- [Servo] It may not be relevant
but did you know that
Gamera's friend to children?
- [Mike] Gamera, oh, he's
made of turtle meat, right?
- [Servo] Yes, really neat.
(loud zing)
(people shout)
- [Crow] I like that very much!
("MST3K Love Theme")
Sir, they called us weenies.
- Sir, we are ready
with the all-wave transmitter.
- [Servo] Ah, sir, you
left an egg on the chair.
- Give me the microphone.
Put Professor Macken
on the screen.
- [Servo] The camera loves him.
- Attention.
People of Earth, I have an
important announcement to make!
One that you've been
waiting for a long time.
Up here with me, I have the
famous Professor Macken!
A name you all recognize who
has agreed to speak to you
on my behalf.
Go ahead, Professor.
- [Servo] Hey, the
Japanese Sylvia Plath.
- [Professor] For
the past 24 hours,
I and several of my
colleagues have been captives
aboard the flagship of
the person who just spoke.
The dictator of Krankor.
For most of that time,
(Mike and robots chuckle)
we have been captive
witnesses of a state
of military technology
capable of destroying any
of the great metropolitan
centers of Earth.
In order to
demonstrate his power,
the dictator intends to
wipe out one of our cities
at noon tomorrow.
The only way to prevent
this is for all nations
and all the governments
of this planet
to agree to accept his terms
for unconditional surrender!
People of Earth, listen to me!
You've only one
response to make!
Bomb the (mumbles)!
- Bomb the ayrower?
- Very good.
- Ayrower!
- Put him back in his quarters.
- [Mike] Get him some ties.
- Put me on the screen.
- Come on, this way.
Get going.
(suspenseful music)
- Alright.
As you can see, your
Professor is indisposed.
So I'll address
you personally.
- Daddy, this is fun!
Go faster!
Raise your hands if
you'd like to go faster!
- [Phantom] And as Professor
Macken has told you,
if I so wished, I could
at this very moment
wipe your entire
city off the map.
- Turn to Full House!
- I can do the same
to New York, Paris,
Rome, Berlin, Moscow!
All of your great
metropolitan centers!
There's nothing to stop me!
For I have completely paralyzed
all of your primitive
defense measures!
Your radar cannot find me,
your fastest jet planes
would be destroyed
the moment they approach
my headquarters.
- The hell is this?
- So you are wise
to keep your war planes grounded
and listen to me
quietly and calmly.
I have come to offer you
a choice between peace
or extermination.
If you do not accept my demand
for unconditional surrender,
I will destroy you.
But if you accept me
willingly as your ruler,
your entire planet will
enter upon a period of peace
and prosperity such
as it has never known
in all its recorded history.
- [Servo] Okay, we give in!
- [Phantom] You have 24 hours
to make your wishes known to me.
I will return tomorrow.
You will tell me then
whether you prefer
(Crow hums)
to surrender or die.
(laughs evilly)
(Tom gasps)
- [Crow] Oh, and we need worms!
(loud zing)
(people scream)
- [Mike] It's going
to rain giblets on us!
- [Servo] The Prince
of Indecision!
- Wally, come on, let's get
out of here, Wally, come on.
- [Crow] Well, back
into the fart mobile.
I still like
bootblacking very much!
(Tom clucks softly)
Come on, slave
labor, I mean kids!
- Chief, Prince is walking away.
We'll follow him.
Go on, follow him.
- [Phantom] Stay with him.
Don't let him out of your sight!
But above all, don't let
him know you are following!
I will be there tonight
and I want to be able
to take him at once!
(soft clucking)
- [Mike] You ever
get the feeling
Krankor is just wingin' it?
- Oh, yeah.
- [Servo] We'll go to a land
where we are free to bootblack!
(suspenseful music)
Buuuck, buuuuuck...
My egg is crowning!
- I wonder how far
he's going to walk.
- Until we stop following him.
- Never mind the jokes.
- Sorry for my zaniness.
- They're going into the house.
(suspenseful music)
- I am going to bootblack
in my room.
- [Crow] Kimmy, don't eat
all the jellied squid!
- [Mike] Cram it, world.
- Ah, home at last.
Good boy, Mickey, gonna
feed the bird, huh?
- What difference does it make?
That mean dictator's gonna
burn us all up anyhow.
- I want the Prince of Space.
He's the only one
who could help us.
- Don't worry, Mickey,
he'll surely help us out.
- You think so?
- Course he will!
He always came before, right?
Didn't he, Mickey?
- Oh, I think he's gone
away and forgotten about us.
- [Servo] The bird left
a letter of resignation.
- Hey!
- [Mike] Leave 50 cuttle
bones under the bridge
or I start spotting your car.
- It's for me.
Dear Mickey, go
to Johnny's house
right away with your sister.
Signed, Prince of Space.
Hey, Wally, what do
you think about that?
- [Kimmy] Listen to what
the note said, Mickey!
- No, wait a minute.
Who could put a note
like this up in a cage?
- Never mind that,
get a move on!
You wanna do what
the note says, right?
- Right, yeah,
come on, let's go.
- [Kimmy] Alright,
goodbye, Wally.
Don't worry about us,
go one with your dinner.
- [Mickey] Hurry,
Kimmy, come on.
- I'm coming, you hurry!
- I love that kid!
Finally, an evening
alone together.
(Mike and robots gasp)
- We got chickens!
(thrilling music)
- [Servo] I don't wanna
be Prince of Space!
- [Crow] Wait,
where are you going?
Come back and let
us capture you!
(Mike and robots
cluck repeatedly)
- [Servo] Exotic locations
like Normandale
Community College!
- The Chief is on
his way to meet us!
What are we gonna do?
- Just keep the
radio beam going.
- [Servo] That's some
hauling ass, whew!
- Halt, or we fire!
- [Crow] Well, his sight's
are pullin' about 60 yards
to the left there. (chuckles)
(Mike and robots cluck loudly)
- [Servo] I brought
grub worms for everyone!
- After 'em that way!
- [Mike] Deploy your tiny
whippers only if necessary!
(eerie twang)
(thrilling music)
- [Servo] Maybe they
just came to this planet
to serve the guy a subpoena.
(loud explosion)
Look at them.
(thrilling music)
Even in death they're
stacked on top of each other.
(Mike and robots cluck loudly)
(loud explosion)
- Ah!
Prince of Space!
- [Servo] I was
thinking it was going
to be Fritz Mondale, but of
course, it's Prince of Space!
(loud explosions)
- Hold your fire!
- You guys look ridiculous!
- Your weapons are useless!
Let's try bare hands now!
- [Mike] Up at 'em,
Prince of Space!
- [Crow] His power
apparently lies
in his choosing
incompetent enemies.
- [Servo] The merchants
are here, we're saved!
They're on to you, I gotta go!
(thrilling music)
The hell?
- [Crow] Oh, hi, cherry, huh?
- You again!
- [Phantom] Yes, it's me!
I've come to finish you off!
- [Crow] What a vicious cycle.
(ray guns zing loudly)
- [Servo] I figure
he'll get bored and die
and then I will rule! (chuckles)
- [Mike] Now even I'm
beginning to doubt my powers.
- (laughs) You see?
How many times do I have
to demonstrate to you?
Your guns are
worthless against me!
- Argh, come closer!
- I'm close enough,
thank you anyway!
The stench of your foul breath
is more than my
stomach can stand!
- Chief, let's go!
- Get away.
Fire, fire!
(thrilling music)
(ray guns fire repeatedly)
- [Crow] Sorry, sir,
you do have bad breath.
- [Servo] I feel good all under!
(ray gun fires repeatedly)
Oh boy, hey wait
up, I need a ride!
I didn't mean that about
your breath, come on!
- [Henchman] Chief, in the stern
window, that flying saucer!
- [Servo] It's Meer, limping
into a service station.
- What do we do?
- Get them out of here!
Put them in their quarters!
- Do it!
- Alright!
Back to your rooms!
- [Crow] Chickens are
too stupid to mutiny.
(thrilling music)
- [Servo] My chest (mumbles)
soap dish will help me.
- [Henchman] What are
we going to do, Chief?
- Let him come.
We'll never survive another
trip through the meteor zone.
But just to make sure,
prepare the costing vapor!
(doors close)
(birds chirping)
- Well, this is good, huh, okay.
Everything seems to
be back to normal.
I'm a befleshed human being
(chuckles) and you guys are--
Oh no.
Oh no!
- Uh, Mike?
Why are we in a sylvan glen?
- (sneezes loudly)
Hey, I got hay fever!
Cool! (laughs)
- I'm gonna--
I'm gonna go lay down
till this all blows over.
I'll see you later.
- I may need a Kleenex!
- You're fine.
(Tom sniffs)
- Poor guy.
He doesn't handle alternate
realities very well, does he?
- (sneezes loudly) Sorry.
(sighs)
- Huh.
- Hm.
- Still, nice day, though.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
(birds chirping)
Fishin'?
- No, thanks.
- Okay.
("MST3K Love Theme")
(Tom groans)
- You okay?
- Yeah, oh God.
- He's heading
right for the center.
Those meteorites will pound
him to pieces in a few minutes.
(laughs evilly)
- [Mike] Yep, I'm the man!
- Alright, I think we've
seen the last of him!
He'll never come
out of that alive!
Give everyone four hours off.
(Mike and robots laugh)
- [Servo] Sir, did
you forget something
when you got dressed
this morning?
- [Mike] Oh, oh, put--
No.
(Tom laughs)
(loud zinging)
- Planet International falls.
(gasps) There he is again!
- [Mike] Just ignoring the fact
they have a giant out there?
- [Servo] The USC losers!
- Just in case, tell the giant
he better keep awake tonight.
You never know.
He might get through
those meteorites.
Bring those Earthlings
into the great hall.
- [Crow] Well, time for our
daily empty threat session!
- [Servo] Krankor will be
with you in a few moments.
Appointments kind
of backed up today.
You can have a seat there.
- Sit down.
Hey, sit down!
Sit down, I told you!
- [Crow] Come on, this
is getting embarrassing!
- What do I have to do?
I told you to sit down!
- [Mike] Oh, you knocked
him slightly off balance.
- [Servo] Must be reported
to Amnesty International!
- [Mike] Or the USDA.
- (chuckles) Maybe
you'll listen to me now.
- [Crow] Chickens
are a cruel people.
(suspenseful music)
- (clears throat) Okay,
who called this meeting?
- I didn't.
- I didn't!
- No.
- We don't?
- [Servo] Lucille?
Whoa!
- [Crow] Get the DeSoto started.
(suspenseful music)
- Hey, what's that?
A rocket!
- [Mike] Oh no, it's
just duct work, okay.
(loud whirring)
(loud clank)
- [Servo] Krankor is
Mary, Queen of Scots.
- [Crow] Taxi!
- [Mike] Go ahead on three.
(Tom gasps in amazement)
- [Crow] Oh, please not this.
Anything but an
old Star Trek set!
- Here, you see Krankor.
A part of my domain which
no man has ever seen.
It is the last thing which
you will see in this life.
- [Mike] So, how are you guys?
- [Doctor] What do you mean?
- [Professor] What
do you mean by that?
- Look!
What's that?
- [Servo] (gasps) Cecil Fielder!
- Do you see that?
What the devil is that?
- It's the monster
which guards this place.
- You hear that?
A monster!
- Quite right, my dear Macken.
A monster which I created.
He obeys my slightest command.
- [Crow] Like wander around
aimlessly and gain weight!
(Mike and Tom chuckle)
- [Henchman] The guardian
has moved into position.
All persons are warned
to stay clear of him.
- Very good.
- Give yourself a star.
- Now, gentlemen,
your time has come.
Prepare to leave Krankor.
- What's that?
- Prepare to leave.
Each of you will
enter a space capsule.
- What?
(Mike laughs)
- Each of you
will enter a space capsule!
- [Phantom] It'll be sealed up.
Each one of you in turn
will then blast off
and travel far, far out
in the furthest reaches
of the galaxy.
- Come again?
- [Phantom] Your course
will be selected at random
and will ultimately
be determined
by the celestial bodies
near which you pass.
- What'd he say?
- Those of you
who are fortunate
will fall into a star.
- How's that?
- The agony will be horrible,
but it will be brief.
- Beg pardon?
- [Phantom] The first
rocket will be manned
by Dr. Macken.
- You know,
wouldn't it cheaper and quicker
to just bludgeon 'em right here?
(Mike grunts)
- [Phantom] Why, Dr.
Macken, you surprise me!
- [Servo] I thought
you were a total puss!
- You look so glum.
After all, you preferred not
to surrender. (laughs evilly)
- [Crow] Hey, don't
moon me over there, hey!
- [Mike] Yup, agonizing
death, no doubt about it.
Yeah.
- [Servo] Sir, we only have
two ships, can we double up?
- What?
The Prince of Space?
- He's coming!
Prince of Space!
He's coming!
- [Servo] Tickets at all
Ticketmaster outlets.
- Oh!
There he is!
(thrilling music)
- Hi, be right with you--
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- What a fool!
- He has defeated us
numerous times, what makes
him think he can do it again?
- The guardian will make
mincemeat out of him!
He'll smash that miserable
fool once and for all!
♪ In the land of Dairy Queen ♪
(loud zinging)
We're closed!
He looks like a welderer
who has fainting spells.
(Mike chuckles)
- [Crow] Ross Perot!
- [Servo] This is starting
to become a weird movie.
Ah, he kills with an
enormous air burp!
- [Mike] Um, what was
that supposed to do?
- [Crow] (chuckles)
It's Pat! (chuckles)
- [Servo] Gonna take a
look at the manual here.
There's giants, ah, big-eared
matronly giants, page 12.
(loud zinging)
- [Crow] Mrs. Robinson, are
you trying to seduce me?
- [Servo] Bless you!
Hmm, what?
- [Mike] Well, not today.
- [Crow] Some monsters
just should not wear belts.
- [Mike] Oh, he's a
yam with features!
(loud zings)
- [Servo] He's gonna
ultra-bright him to death!
♪ What would you say
if I sang out of tune ♪
(loud whirring)
- [Mike] I'll circle in and
get it some of that plaque.
(twanging sound)
- [Phantom] Attention, gunners!
Blast him with every
available battery!
Automatic track and fire!
- [Servo] Okay, a little
this, a little that,
strike up to this over here...
(loud explosions)
Oh!
- [Crow] Is this worth it--
Ha-ha, no I'll save it.
(Phantom laughs evilly)
- [Phantom] So much for
that Prince of Space!
Nothing, not even he can
resist the devastating effect
of my thorian bombs.
- What?
- [Phantom] Now, let's get
on with our ceremony, eh?
(laughs evilly)
- Oh, don't.
Doesn't he realize
how forced it sounds?
Ugh, those eggs.
- Alright, Macken.
You first, get a move on!
- No!
Don't take Macken!
- [Crow] Now we isolate
our first contestant
in a soundproof booth!
- Leave him alone!
- Hey! What are you doing?
(doctors shout at the same time)
- [Mike] Another beer here.
(loud zinging)
- [Servo] Back to
my dry goods stores.
- [Crow] (chuckles)
Seeing these guys,
it's hard to believe human
beings ever have sex.
(loud zinging)
(henchman gasps)
- No!
- He wasn't killed!
- What?
(thrilling music)
- Hello!
- Prince of Space!
You're still alive, are you?
- Of course I am.
And I will keep fighting
to protect the people
who call upon me
to save them from
your domination!
- Blast him!
(loud zinging)
- [Servo] Ah, I
didn't say blast,
I said rest him, rest him,
- Listen!
I call upon you to surrender!
To release these Earthlings!
To return them to wherever
you took them from
and to cease your evil
plotting once and for all!
- [Mike] You can't see me!
(thrilling music)
(loud racket)
- Come on, Professor!
- Prince of Space!
- [Servo] It's Michael Jeter,
of course it's Prince of Space!
(loud explosion)
(loud zinging)
- [Mike] Oh, our
collective headaches!
- [Crow] Mouse trap!
(robots hum)
("MST3K Love Theme")
- You, turn off
the reserve power!
Switch on the heating
current to that griddle!
Now that I've got him I'm
gonna broil him alive!
(laughs evilly)
- [Crow] I hope he has his
tanning goggles on! (laughs)
(loud whirring)
- Here come the deadly
fly rod cases.
- [Servo] Dearly beloved,
we are gathered here
to get through this
thing called life!
(loud whirring)
- [Mike] Careful,
sweetie, no rain.
- [Crow] Gentlemen,
prepare to be super soaked!
- [Mike] No one can
resist my, uh, things!
- [Servo] Rapid deployment
system leaves no time
to react!
- [Crow] Yeah, the
things are comin' out.
Come on out, varmint!
- [Mike] Shouldn't have
let Mom make my costume!
I am saving up such a laugh.
- He's well cooked.
Enough!
- Right!
- [Servo] Steamed
Prince of Space
or fried and beer-battered?
- (gasps) Prince is alive!
- D'oh! I was hidin' here!
- Enough of this!
When will you ever learn?
Your guns won't work on me?
- Kill him!
(Crow groans)
- [Mike] (chuckles)
New plan, sir!
- Fire lasers!
(loud zinging)
- [Crow] C'mon, movie's over.
Let's just go.
(loud zinging)
- Put Debbie on hold for a sec.
- [Mike] Sick,
angry, a turtle...
(thrilling music)
(loud zinging)
- [Crow] Oh, I suppose
that's it for me!
Yup, I'm dead.
- Give up?
Or I have to kill you!
(loud zinging)
- Well, I can't back that up!
(loud explosions)
- No!
- [Mike] You'll never
defeat me, bye now!
- [Crow] Into the giblet mobile!
(thrilling music)
- Now's our chance!
Come on, follow me!
- Yes!
- [Servo] I have no
objective whatsoever!
- [Doctor] Where are you going?
- Follow me! Quickly!
C'mon, c'mon!
- Follow him!
(thrilling music)
- [Servo] We'll just run
potty and then we'll go!
- [Crow] Mike, I swear
I am never gonna forget
what the Japanese did
to us with this movie.
- Come on, this way!
- [Prince] No, wait, look out!
(Mike and robots gasp)
- We're trapped!
- Not yet, come, this way!
- No, wait, stop!
- What?
- [Servo] Wait, stop, this way!
Now, run! No, wait!
Come on, no look out!
Wait, stop!
- [Mike] Prince of Space!
- Hurry!
Come this way!
- No, wait!
Is that the way out?
- Of course, come on!
- [Crow] Wait!
Probably it isn't!
No, I'll follow you!
Wait, Prince of Space!
- [Servo] The Ritz
Brothers have more dignity!
(doctors shout at the same time)
- Calm down!
- [Servo] Okay, now panic.
- Caught like rats in a trap!
You'll be safe enough here.
I'm leaving for Earth now.
But when I come back, I'll have
a very special kind
of death for you,
my dear Prince of Space!
Goodbye.
- [Crow] So he
has a quick errand
before he kills Prince of Space.
- [Servo] What, what
are you lookin' at?
- I had a very good reason
for not killing him now.
He's going to prepare for
blast off in his flagship.
And unfortunately it's
the only ship available
that will take
you back to Earth.
Now, all of you
stay close behind me
and do exactly what
I tell you to do.
(loud zinging)
- Okay, now watch more.
There you go.
- [Servo] Some more,
yes, good watching...
- [Crow] My grill
lighter is saving us!
- [Servo] Oh, we are
more interested now!
- [Mike] Why is he melting
semi-sweet chocolate?
- [Crow] (chuckles) Hey,
guys, watch this, watch this.
My arthritis!
Oh, my spastic colon!
- Oh, my gout!
- Oh, my bad knee!
- Oh, my baldness!
(thrilling music)
- [Crow] Prince of
Crossing Guards!
- [Servo] Would you get
back further, you morons!
- [Prince] Stop
right where you are!
(henchmen shout
at the same time)
- Oh, I love him!
- Let's get his autograph!
- You fools, he's all alone!
- Stand where you are!
The first man who walks down
the ramp will be signing
his own death warrant!
I've booby trapped
the whole thing
and your own thorian
bombs will blast you
into the next world!
- You lie.
- You can find out
pretty easily whether I'm
telling you the truth.
Look behind you
in that corridor.
- [Crow] Oh, gross,
stain in the rug!
- Alright, then I surrender!
- [Servo] They
locked themselves.
- [Prince] Get back,
get out of sight!
- Capture them for hostages!
- [Crow] So no accumulated
memory whatsoever!
- Come on.
Why don't you try
to board your ship?
- Why you!
- Your brother's bad, too!
- Oh, Prince! (mumbles)
Are you alright?
- Quiet down.
We haven't a moment to lose!
Everybody board the
ship right away!
- What about you?
- I will stay here till
you're safe on your way.
(loud racket)
- What's that?
- Go on, hurry!
- Run!
- Yes, yes!
- [Crow] Next, the
Prince will sew name tags
in their underwear.
Bunch of babies.
Yeah, I need those guys like I
need another one-inch wiener!
(thrilling music)
- Keep pushing, men!
We're almost out
of our atmosphere!
(loud explosion)
(Mike grunts and groans)
(loud screams)
(loud explosion)
- [Crow] My coup!
My beautiful,
beautiful coup! (sobs)
(robots cluck sadly)
- [Mike] If we'd
built this up to code,
this never would have happened!
(loud explosion)
- Ah yes.
The ancient Japanese
tradition of blowing up models
at the end of the movie!
- [Mike] The blast of these
bedrock claim the lives
of Frederick R. Flintstone
and Barnabas Rubble today.
(loud zinging)
- [Crow] And a proud,
noble civilization
dies out sometimes.
This loser civilization,
however, will not be missed!
- Dr. Macken, Dr. Macken!
- [Servo] I'm wet again!
- The other mag pilot's
working perfectly!
We're on a direct
course for Earth!
- Wonderful!
- And look there
on the visual screen!
The one we owe everything to!
- (gasps) It's the
Prince of Space!
He wouldn't even
let us say thanks.
Who knows if we'll
ever see him again?
- Say, we'd better radio ahead.
Tell the others we're safe
and we're coming home!
Thanks to Prince of Space!
(doctors agree at the same time)
- [Servo] On their own,
the giant infant scientists
survived another minute
and then crashed.
- [Mike] Meanwhile
all the boot centers
get duller and less black.
- [Crow] And yet,
I feel so empty.
- [Servo] You know,
this movie made me
wanna renounce my Toyota.
Oh, it's the end!
This movie cannon's
enough for me!
- [Mike] But it's
Prince of Space!
(doors close)
- Okay, okay, okay.
I'm a satellite of
love, right, right?
There's no time lags, Mike's
not a puny little robot.
- Nope, I--
Well, I don't think so.
- 'Cause I tell you guys,
you get to the point
where you just wanna go,
"Wormhole, back off!"
- No, I hear you.
But it seems like
everything's back to normal.
Oh, you guys know
my wife, Krankor.
(robots scream)
- Get me outta here!
(Phantom laughs evilly)
- (laughs) That was good!
We got 'em, Krankor,
thanks a lot!
- We certainly got them
that time! (laughs evilly)
- Yeah.
Yeah, well, there's no reason
for you to hang around.
You can take off.
- They ran like fools!
(laughs evilly)
- Yeah, I guess
they did, Krankor.
- We pulled the wool
over their eyes!
(laughs evilly)
- You know what,
Krankor wants to leave, alright?
- Oh, do you?
Well, you may be
interested to know
that I've already conquered
your puny satellite
and then you have no defense--
(Mike shouts)
Oh, oh! Oh, please
don't hurt me!
- Krankor.
- Mike, Crow, Servo, Krankor!
We're orbiting the planet
that looks like ours!
- Earth, wow!
- Not sure.
- Oh, really?
- Yes!
- It is?
- I think.
- Would you knock
it off, Mrs. F.
How about you?
Do you know where we
are or when we are?
- I don't know, Mike.
There's no sign of Bobo but
there are marble columns
and intricate frescoes.
- Evidently a sewage
system of some sort.
- Could it possibly be--
(trumpets blare)
- Welcome to Roman Times!
- Guards! (claps)
Seize them!
(thrilling music)